frogdesign.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy | frog

Your privacy is very important to us. This notice explains our online information collection practices and the choices available to you about the way your information is used at our website.

## Information We Collect

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you (your name, telephone, address, e-mail, etc.) unless you provide us that information when you fill request some information from us, if you register to attend a company event, subscribe to a newsletter, or if you submit an employment application in response to a job posting on our website. We do automatically collect certain non-personal information when you visit our website, such as the type of browser and operating system you are using, and the domain name of your internet service provider (such as Comcast, AT&T).

## How We Use Information We Collect About You

We use non-personally identifiable information to analyze site usage (aggregated information about which pages were visited by our users) in order to improve the design and content of our website.

When personal information is collected, we will inform you at the point of collection the purpose for the collection. We use personally identifiable information you provide only to respond to your inquiries or to register for programs and events that are sponsored by or co-sponsored by other organizations. Should you elect to register electronically for any such programs or events, we have no control over the third party sponsor's use of your information, as the privacy policy on our website will not apply.

Any information gathered by us may be shared, if appropriate, with any frog offices, affiliates and subsidiaries throughout the world. Personal information which users in the European Union provide to us may be transferred to other countries (including the United States). The data protection and privacy laws of such countries may differ from those of the European Union, and by providing your information to us, you expressly agree to such transfer.

We will not contact you about other matters, unless you specifically request it, nor will we share, distribute or sell your personally identifiable information outside of frog and its affiliates and subsidiaries, except that frog may also share your information with third parties if we collect your information to register you for a company event or register for a newsletter and such third party must receive your information for registration purposes.

Whenever possible, we will provide you with the opportunity to "opt in" prior to receiving direct marketing or market research information. This means we will require your affirmative consent before we use your information for purposes other than the purpose for which it was submitted.

If you apply for a job at frog, and submit a resume by e-mail or through our website, we will use the resume only for an internal application review process.

It is possible that we might be forced to disclose your personally identifiable information in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith such disclosure is required by law, such as in response to a court order, a law enforcement agency request, in response to a subpoena, or in response to an administrative agency's request.

Although we employ security measures to prevent unauthorized access to information we collect online, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information. Specifically, we cannot guarantee the privacy of personal information you transmit over the web, or that may be collected in transit by third parties, including any consultants that provide services to us.

## Collection of Information by Third Party Sites.

Like many other commercial websites, our site contains links to other sites whose information collection practices may be different than ours. Users should consult the other sites' privacy notices, as we do not have any control over any information that may be submitted to or collected by such third parties.

## Cookies.

A cookie is a text-only string of information that a website transfers to the “cookies” file of the browser on your computer's hard disk in order that the website can remember you when you return for another visit to the site. A cookie contains the name of the domain from which the cookie originated, how long the cookie will remain active, and a randomly generated unique number to track pages you have visited. Every time you visit our site, we send you a cookie in order to track traffic to our site. Cookies may be used to enable the personalization features of our site (you can recall recently-viewed pages, and have information that you have previously provided be filled in automatically instead of having to fill in registration questionnaires every time), and to compile anonymous aggregate data that allow us to determine how visitors use our site and help us improve our offerings on the website. We may use session cookies (temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the site) and persistent cookies (remain in your browser for a longer period of time, depending on the “lifetime” of the cookie) on this website.

If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of the frog website if you do so. In particular, you may be required to accept cookies in order to complete certain actions on our website. You do not need to have cookies turned on, however, to use/navigate through many parts of our website, except access to certain of frog's web pages that require a login and password.

## Revisions to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to amend this policy or any part of it from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site or updating this policy. Please review the policy periodically for changes.

## How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy or its implementation, please contact us at [info@frogdesign.com](mailto:info@frogdesign.com). If at any time you decide that we should no longer retain your personal information, please let us know by e-mailing us at the above address.

This Privacy Policy was last updated May 12, 2012.
